you guys this looks like a fun one it
says solve for x that's the square root
of x to the X to the x equals X and it
says X is greater than one so it does
look like x equals one would have been
one solution for this but they've
excluded that solution and they want us
to find another one if you want to try
this on your own pause it right now
because I'm going to solve it in three
two one so first we can multiply these
exponents at x times x is equal to x
squared and next to get rid of this
square root let's Square both sides of
the equation so this exponent and this
square root are going to cancel each
other out so now we have x to the x
squared equals x squared since X can't
equal one or zero that means the only
way this is true is if the exponents are
equal to each other so we can drop the
base Drop the Base
so we can drop the bass and set the
exponents equal to each other and then
from here we can square root both sides
and the square root of x squared is the
absolute value of x so we have the
absolute value of x is equal to square
root of 2 but since we know that X can't
be negative this is just going to be x
equals square root of 2 and that is the
answer to our question we can put a box
around it and let's check our work we're
going to plug in the square root of 2
for each of these x's and then we're
going to multiply these exponents square
root of 2 times square root of 2 is
equal to two and then this square root
and this Square cancel each other out
and then we end up with square root of 2
equals square root of 2 it checks out so
for this problem x equals the square
root of two how exciting